HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Communications Department Files
1985-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/005
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records.
6273256
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 22, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 AV: HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 MB: HERE Memorabilia 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/001: HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/002: HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/003: HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf: HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files 6199/015: HERE Editor Files
Hotels -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Restaurants -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Hospitality industry -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Hanley, Edward T.; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union; Hotel, Hospital, Restaurant, and Tavern Employees' Union
6273256
- Catering Industry Employees., 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence.
- Catering Industry Employees. (folder 1), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Publications and Clippings. (2 diskettes)
- Catering Industry Employees. (folder 2), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Publications and Clippings.
- Catering Industry Employees (Canada)., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Correspondence and News.
- Corcoran School and Catering Industry Employees., 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  News Releases.
- Culinary Alliance and Bartenders Union., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Local 425 (Vancouver, WA).
- Culinary Industry Employees., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Local 400 (Spokane, WA).
- Culinary Workers., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Clippings.
- HERE Hearings., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hanley, Edward T. President of Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. (folder 1), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hanley, Edward T. President of Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. (folder 2), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  News Releases. (diskette)
- Hanley, Edward T. Press Releases, Speeches., 1973-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Hanley, Edward T. President's Record Vindicated., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Hanley, Edward T. News and Magazine, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Articles.
- Hanley, Edward T., 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  News Clippings.
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Correspondence and Testimony.
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  List of Local Editors.
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Local 457 (Everett, WA).
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1980-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Local 483 (Monterey, CA).
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Local 535 (Riverside, CA).
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Local 569 (Cumberland, MD).
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Local 634 (Philadelphia, PA).
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Local 737 (Orlando, FL).
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. (folder 1), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  News.
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. (folder 2), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Union Publication.
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. Union Publication. (folder 1), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Edited.
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. Union Publication. (folder 2), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Local 26. Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Local 737. Catering Industry Employees., 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Local 226. Culinary Workers Union. Union, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Booklets and Clippings.
- Magazines of Various Unions., 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- NAACP Show., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- New Yorker. Maids in the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Niagara Casino., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- PR Newswire., 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Palm Springs., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Post Office. Circulation Form. CIE., 1983-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Press Releases., 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Reno Organizing., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Rerum Novarum Awards., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Testimony., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Third Class Mail., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Union Industries Show., 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "Union Yes" Campaign., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Unionized Houses., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- United States Post Office., 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Wage Laws., 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Waiters/Waitresses., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Waiters and Waitresses Race. (folder 1), 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Waiters and Waitresses Race. (folder 2), 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Wilhelm-Gaming Study., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Williamsburg Organizing., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Women. (folder 1), 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Women. (folder 2), 1970-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Frank Alexander Files (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Clippings (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Congressional Investigation [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Congressional Investigation [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Duluth Cooks Apprenticeship Standards (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Railroads, History (Box 3, Folder 6)
- A Return to Half-Truth and Innuendo, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)